<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conceptual representation on Xuan Pan</title>
    <link>https://xpan55.github.io/tags/conceptual-representation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conceptual representation on Xuan Pan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://xpan55.github.io/tags/conceptual-representation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conceptual Representations of Culturally-loaded Animals in Bilinguals</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on the Journal of Cultural Cognitive Science:
Pan, X. &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2021). Cross-language activation of culture-specific features in Chinese-English bilinguals. Journal of Cultural Cognitive Science, 5, 325–344.
and has been presented at the Psychonomics Society 2019 Annual Meeting, Montréal, Canada:
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2019, November). Conceptual representations of culturally-loaded animals in Chinese-English bilinguals. The Psychonomics Society 2019 Annual Meeting, Montréal, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexical Conceptual Representations in Bicultural Bilinguals</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project4/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on Bilingualism: Language and Cognition:
Pan, X., Xiong, A., Jouravlev, O., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2021). Conceptual representations in bicultural bilinguals: An ERP approach. Bilingualism: Language and Cognition, 24(5), 932–944.
and has been presented at the Psychonomics Society 2015 Annual Meeting, Chicago, USA:
Jared, D., Xiong, A., Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jouravlev, O. (2015, November). Lexical conceptual representations in bicultural bilinguals. The Psychonomics Society 2015 Annual Meeting, Chicago, USA.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
