<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xuan Pan</title>
    <link>https://xpan55.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xuan Pan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xpan55.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Cognitive Shifting and Intelligence on Creativity</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on the Journal of Creative Behavior:
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Yu, H. (2016). Different effects of cognitive shifting and intelligence on creativity. Journal of Creative Behavior, 52(3), 212–225.
and has been presented at the Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science 2015 annual meeting, Ottawa, Canada.:
Pan, X. (2015, June). The relationship between creativity and cognitive switching: Mediating effect of intelligence. Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science, Ottawa, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Linguistic Labels on Object Categorization and Perception.</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on Bilingualism: Language and Cognition amd Language and Cognition:
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2021). Effects of Chinese word structure on object perception in Chinese- English bilinguals: Evidence from an ERP visual oddball paradigm. Bilingualism: Language and Cognition, 24(1), 111–123.
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2020). Effects of Chinese word structure on object categorization in Chinese-English bilinguals. Language and Cognition, 12(3), 468–500.
and has been presented at Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science 2019 annual meeting, Waterloo, Canada, and the 11th International Conference on The Mental Lexicon, Edmonton, Canada:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An online Self-Paced Rading (SPR) Task Demo</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project3/</guid>
      <description>Online Self-Paced Reading
Participants read the sentences in an online moving window SPR task in which they control their own pace of reading by pressing the spacebar. Data were collected on how long (in ms) it takes to read each word in the sentence.
Click HERE for a demo of the online SPR task in English.
(The experiment was created with PsychoPy and hosted on Pavlovia.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TBA</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>TBA </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xuan Pan, Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>As a research scientist with 8+ years of experience in language-cognition interaction and bilingualism, I am experienced with examining human behaviours through carefully designed experiments.
As a data analyst with 8+ years of experience with SPSS, R, and SQL, I am passionate about making sense of complex data and telling stories that help people derive insight.
As a newbie birder, WOW and OMG, why didn&amp;rsquo;t I notice there are so many lovely birds around me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xuan Pan, Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Email: xuanpan1105@gmail.com Education Ph.D. Cognitive Psychology and Neuroscience 2019 University of Western Ontario, London, Ontario. 2014-2019.
Thesis: The effects of linguistic labels on object categorization and perception.
Analyzed and visualized both behavioural (response times and accuracy) and neural (electroencephalogram brain waves) data using R and MATLAB. M.Ed. Cognitive Psychology and Neuroscience 2014 Nanjing Normal University, Nanjing, China. 2011-2014
Thesis: The effects of cognitive switching on creative thinking: Mediating impact of intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
