<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Xuan Pan</title>
    <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Xuan Pan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://xpan55.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Cognitive Shifting and Intelligence on Creativity</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on the Journal of Creative Behavior:
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Yu, H. (2016). Different effects of cognitive shifting and intelligence on creativity. Journal of Creative Behavior, 52(3), 212–225.
and has been presented at the Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science 2015 annual meeting, Ottawa, Canada.:
Pan, X. (2015, June). The relationship between creativity and cognitive switching: Mediating effect of intelligence. Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science, Ottawa, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Linguistic Labels on Object Categorization and Perception.</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>This project has been published on Bilingualism: Language and Cognition amd Language and Cognition:
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2021). Effects of Chinese word structure on object perception in Chinese- English bilinguals: Evidence from an ERP visual oddball paradigm. Bilingualism: Language and Cognition, 24(1), 111–123.
Pan, X., &amp;amp; Jared, D. (2020). Effects of Chinese word structure on object categorization in Chinese-English bilinguals. Language and Cognition, 12(3), 468–500.
and has been presented at Canadian Society for Brain, Behaviour and Cognitive Science 2019 annual meeting, Waterloo, Canada, and the 11th International Conference on The Mental Lexicon, Edmonton, Canada:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An online Self-Paced Rading (SPR) Task Demo</title>
      <link>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xpan55.github.io/project/project3/</guid>
      <description>Online Self-Paced Reading
Participants read the sentences in an online moving window SPR task in which they control their own pace of reading by pressing the spacebar. Data were collected on how long (in ms) it takes to read each word in the sentence.
Click HERE for a demo of the online SPR task in English.
(The experiment was created with PsychoPy and hosted on Pavlovia.)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
